
// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Everybody _____ Raymond.",
    answer: "Loves",
    options: [
      "Loved",
      "Loves",
      "Love",
      "Loving"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "We ____ won it all!",
    answer: "Have",
    options: [
      "Have",
      "Had",
      "Has",
      "Haven"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Neither Tiana nor I _____ coming with you.",
    answer: "Am",
    options: [
      "Will",
      "Am",
      "Is",
      "Would"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "A jar of hearts ____ on the counter.",
    answer: "Is",
    options: [
      "Are",
      "Were",
      "Is",
      "Will"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Each phone ____ costs $168.",
    answer: "Costs",
    options: [
      "Cost",
      "Costs",
      "Corst",
      "Corts"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "There are many other ___ to support my point.",
    answer: "Examples",
    options: [
      "Example",
      "Ecxample",
      "Examples",
      "Exmples"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Where are the cookies that ___ in the cookie jar?",
    answer: "Were",
    options: [
      "Was",
      "Were",
      "Are",
      "Is"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Each of the three little bags ___ stolen.",
    answer: "Was",
    options: [
      "Was",
      "Were",
      "Is",
      "Are"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Every Bently, Lamborghini, and Porche here ___ owned by him.",
    answer: "Is",
    options: [
      "Is",
      "Are",
      "Was",
      "Will"
    ]
  },


      {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Dayo ___ to code",
    answer: "Loves",
    options: [
      "Loves",
      "Love",
      "Loved",
      "Loving"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 11,
    question: " If 3x + 3y = 4 what is the value of 21x + 21y?",
    answer: "4/9",
    options: [
      "36",
      "24",
      "4/9",
      "9/4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What is the cubic root of 64",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "14",
      "4",
      "16",
      "2"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "The x axis on the carteesian plane is?",
    answer: "Horizontal",
    options: [
      "Vetical",
      "Diagonal",
      "Horizontal",
      "Not a line"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Angle at a point measures?",
    answer: "360 deg",
    options: [
      "180 deg",
      "720 deg",
      "360 deg",
      "90 deg"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The log of 64 to the base of 2 is?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "7",
      "5",
      "6",
      "8"
    ]
  },
  
      {
    numb: 16,
    question: "If x equals 30, what is the half of x squared",
    answer: "225",
    options: [
      "900",
      "225",
      "169",
      "144"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 17,
    question: "What is the fourth term of the geometric progression 32,16,8...",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "6",
      "4",
      "8",
      "2"
    ]
  },



      {
    numb: 18,
    question: "What is 2 plus 2?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "22",
      "2",
      "4",
      "44"
    ]
  },


      {
    numb: 19,
    question: "The longest side of a right angled triangle is called the?",
    answer: "Hypotenus",
    options: [
      "Quadrant",
      "Hypotenus",
      "Diagonal",
      "Slope"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 20,
    question: "What is the value of 105:15",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "15",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ]
  },

   ];
  
